<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Almir Dzinovic&#39;s Corner</title>
    <link>https://dzinovic.net/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Almir Dzinovic&#39;s Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2010-2018 by &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzinovic.net&#34;&gt;Almir Dzinovic&#39;s Corner&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dzinovic.net/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VirtualBox on headless CentOS 6</title>
      <link>https://dzinovic.net/post/virtualbox-on-centos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dzinovic.net/post/virtualbox-on-centos/</guid>
      <description>Due to the need to install a server which will be used mainly for hosting virtual machines, but also be capable to provide other services, such as being FTP and Samba server, I decided to go with the CentOS Linux, without having X windows and such unnecessary things installed, Oracle&amp;rsquo;s VirtualBox, and the PHP front-end for it called phpVirtualBox. Anyway, to make a long story short, here&amp;rsquo;s how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware VMs Linux startup script</title>
      <link>https://dzinovic.net/post/vmware-vms-linux-startup-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dzinovic.net/post/vmware-vms-linux-startup-script/</guid>
      <description>Once the hardware on my home PC got upgraded I decided to run a couple of virtual machines on it at all times.
I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen VMware Workstation for the job, considering that, as a VCP, I have a license for it. Underneath it is Ubuntu Linux 11.04 64-bit.
Now, because I like it all to be automatic I&amp;rsquo;ve written this little script which uses the vmrun command to start and stop my virtual machines automatically during the boot-up and shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust File Copy Front End</title>
      <link>https://dzinovic.net/post/robust-file-copy-front-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dzinovic.net/post/robust-file-copy-front-end/</guid>
      <description>This is meant to be the home page for my recent project Robust File Copy Front End, or RFCFE.

This project arised from my extensive use of the robocopy command on Windows and wish to develop something using C# (even though I&amp;rsquo;m not really a developer). I know there already is a robocopy front end from TechNet, which is free, and even one (or more of them) that should be payed for, but I guessed one more won&amp;rsquo;t hurt, especially since this one is completely open sourced and GPL&amp;rsquo;d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quake-style Terminal for Windows</title>
      <link>https://dzinovic.net/post/quake-style-terminal-for-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dzinovic.net/post/quake-style-terminal-for-windows/</guid>
      <description>How it all started&amp;hellip; Well, first things first&amp;hellip;
After using Linux for many years now I got used to the tool called YaKuake. It&amp;rsquo;s a quake-like console that can be set to start upon logging in and to be scrolled down and hidden just by pressing F12. This proved to be very useful tool that I practically got hooked on. Now, beeing sometimes (well, most of the times lately) forced to use Windows I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to find something similar to this, and then I bumped into this and by using the instructions and tools provided there I managed to fix up this little thingie I called &amp;ldquo;Quake-style Terminal for Windows&amp;rdquo; (not quite intuitive, I have to admit, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t come up with anything better at the time).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>